Al Khdhairi Kanaan Frontend Developer

≥ alkhdhairikanaan@gmail.com

• Vienna, Austria

S live:.cid.bcf23391617035d8

Profile

I'm an experienced front-end developer with a solid background in everything related to online marketing on top. It is my passion to build sleek & well-optimized optimized websites and web apps. I'm very much into gaming and learning to work with new technologies, always improving myself to stay on top of my field. Further, I like nature and enjoy doing some trekking from time to time. Finally, I'm a good person to have a beer with.

Skills

Responsive Web Design	• • • • •
JavaScript & TypeScript	• • • • •
React.js	• • • • •
Angular.js	• • • • •
Vue.js & Svelte	• • • • •
WordPress & Shopify	• • • • •
PHP & Laravel	• • • • •
Node.js & Express	• • • • •
MySQL	• • • • •
MongoDB	• • • • •

Languages

English

B2

Education

Bachelor's degree of Computer Science

Vienna University of Technology 2012/01 – 2015/07 +8038109003

in www.linkedin.com/in/al-khdhairikanaan-994a002a4

Professional Experience

Office Manager

Camels

2015/07 - 2017/05 | Vienna, Austria

Main areas of application:

Technical infrastructure and website maintenance, office administration and organization,

Seminar operation

Seminar organization:

Preparation of advertising measures (advertisements, banner advertising, print templates), social media support,

Newsletter creation and sending

GDPR:

Significant participation in the creation a data protection declaration, processing of order processing contracts

Accounting:

Accounting preparation for the Tax advice

Junior Software Developer

CODERS.BAY Vienna

2017/07 - 2021/02 | Vienna, Austria

Frontend Developer

Parvan Pajooh

2021/02 - 2022/12 | Tehran, Iran

Worked with advanced web development technologies like React, Typescript, JavaScript, Bootstrap 4, CSS, SASS, and HTML.

Worked with several React UI libraries like Ant design and Material UI.

Created compatible customer client dashboards.

Worked with UX/UI design teams to improve existing applications.

used Jira tool for requirement gathering, GitHub, and Git Lab as version control systems.

used multiple state management like Redux, Context, Recoil

Frontend Developer

Bühler Group

2022/12 - present | Vienna, Austria